// export const quizData = [
//     {
//       id: 0,
//       question: ` What is the Capital Of India ?`,
//       options: [`New Delhi`, `Mumbai`, `Kolkatta`],
//       answer: `New Delhi`
//     },
//     {
//       id: 1,
//       question: `Who is the CEO of Tesla Motors?`,
//       options: [`Bill Gates`, `Steve Jobs`, `Elon Musk`],
//       answer: `Elon Musk`
//     },
//     {
//       id: 3,
//       question: `Name World's Richest Man?`,
//       options: [`Jeff Bezo`, `Bill Gates`, `Mark Zuckerberg`],
//       answer: `Jeff Bezo`
//     },
//     {
//       id: 4,
//       question: `World's Longest River?`,
//       options: [`River Nile`, `River Amazon`, `River Godavari`],
//       answer: `River Nile`
//     }
//   ];
export const quizData = [
  {
    id: "0",
    question: `Diabetes`,
    options: [`Yes`, `No`],
    answer: `New Delhi`
  },
  {
    id: "1",
    question: `Hypertension`,
    options: [`Yes`, `No`],
    answer: `Elon Musk`
  },
  {
    id: "2",
    question: `Smoking`,
    options: [`Yes`, `No`],
    answer: `Yes`
  },
  {
    id: "3",
    question: `Obesity`,
    options: [`Yes`, `No`],
    answer: `River Nile`
  },
  {
    id: "4",
    question: `Lack of physical activity`,
    options: [`Yes`, `No`],
    answer: `River Nile`
  },
  {
    id: "5",
    question: ` Alcohol`,
    options: [`Yes`, `No`],
    answer: `Yes`
  },
  {
    id: "6",
    question: `If female Post Menopausal`,
    options: [`Yes`, `No`],
    answer: `River Nile`
  },
  {
    id: "7",
    question: `Consumption of fruits daily`,
    options: [`Yes`, `No`],
    answer: `River Nile`
  },
  {
    id: "8",
    question: `Chronic Kidney Disease`,
    options: [`Yes`, `No`],
    answer: `River Nile`
  },
  {
    id: "9",
    question: `Chest Pain`,
    options: [`Yes`, `No`],
    answer: `Yes`
  },
  {
    id: "10",
    question: `Pain or discomfort in one or both arms`,
    options: [`Yes`, `No`],
    answer: `River Nile`
  },
  {
    id: "11",
    question: `Pain or discomfort in Jaw neck,back or stomach`,
    options: [`Yes`, `No`],
    answer: `River Nile`
  },
  {
    id: "12",
    question: `Sweating`,
    options: [`Yes`, `No`],
    answer: `River Nile`
  },
  {
    id: "13",
    question: `Shortness of breathe or cough at night`,
    options: [`Yes`, `No`],
    answer: `River Nile`
  },
  {
    id: "14",
    question: `Swelling of lower limbs`,
    options: [`Yes`, `No`],
    answer: `River Nile`
  },
  {
    id: "15",
    question: `Loss of consciousness`,
    options: [`Yes`, `No`],
    answer: `Yes`
  },
  
  {
    id: "16",
    question: `Post procedure complications`,
    options: [`Black tarry stools`, `Skin rashes`,`Muscle pain`,`Swelling at sight of procedure`,`None`],
    answer: `None`
  },
  {
    id: "17",
    question: `Medication`,
    options: [`Yes`, `No`],
    answer: `Yes`
  },
  {
    id: "18",
    question: `Smoking`,
    options: [`Yes`, `No`],
    answer: `Yes`
  },


  {
    id: "19",
    question: ` Alcohol`,
    options: [`Yes`, `No`],
    answer: `Yes`
  },
  
  {
    id: "20",
    question: `Diet (Fruits,pulses and vegetables)`,
    options: [`Yes`, `No`],
    answer: `No`
  },
  {
    id: "21",
    question: `Regular OPD follow up`,
    options: [`Yes`, `No`],
    answer: `River Nile`
  }
];

